现在是新闻报道
This is Media-Break.
只需要三分钟就就可以从这里了解世界
You give us three minutes and we'll give you the world.
早上好 现在由凯西王和杰斯伯金斯为您报道
Good morning, I'm Casey Wong with Jess Perkins.
首先是关于南非比勒陀利亚的报道
Top story, Pretoria.
今天南非反对核武器的运动升级
The threat of nuclear confrontation in South Africa escalated today...
被围困的军人政府
...when the military government of that besieged city-state...
公开了一枚法制中子弹
...unveiled a French-made neutron bomb...
并扬言会作为最后的武器使用
...and affirmed that it would use it as the city's last line of defense.
今天总统第一次在星球大战
The president's first press conference
防御平台上召开新闻发布会
from the Star Wars Peace Platform...
但由于准备不充分 电力中断
...got off to a shaky start when power failed...
使得总统和其随从出于失重状态
...causing a period of weightlessness for the president and his staff.
稍后再见
We'll be back in a moment.
要做大手术了吗?
Is it time for that operation?
这或许是你一生中最重要的决定
This may be the most important decision of your life.
来和我们经验丰富的外科医生谈谈
So come down and talk to one of our qualified surgeons...
在家庭心脏中心
...at the Family Heart Center.
我们有一些列由延森和雅马哈联合制造的人工心脏
We feature the complete line of hearts by Jensen and Yamaha.
请购买我们生产的心脏
You pick the heart.
物美价廉
Extended warranties. Financing.
国药准字号
Qualifies for health tax credit.
请记住 我们一直在关心您的健康
And remember, we care.
三名警官殉职 一名受重伤
Three dead police officers, one critically injured.
警方高层指责全销公司 简称OCP
Police leaders blame Omni Consumer Products, OCP...
此公司最近与底特律政府达成
...the firm which recently agreed with the city to fund and run...
接管底特律警察局的协议
...the Detroit Metro Police Department.
这是OCP的总裁迪克·琼斯的讲话:
Dick Jones, president of OCP.
每个警察都知道他们的工作会有危险
Every policeman knows there are inherent risks in his job.
如果你承受不了 最好回家去
If you can't stand the heat, you better stay out of the kitchen.
弗莱德瑞克森警员虽然受伤了 但他逃脱并认出了凶手
Although wounded, Officer Frederickson escaped and identified this man.
克拉伦斯·伯蒂迪克是底特律旧城区的刑事犯罪头子
Clarence Boddicker, unofficial crime boss of Old Detroit...
据调查他涉嫌杀害三十一名警员
...sought in connection with the deaths of 31 officers.
现在他仍在逃 而此时亨利福特医院的医生
Today he is free while doctors at Henry Ford Hospital...
正全力抢救弗兰克弗莱德瑞克森警员
...fight to save Officer Frank Frederickson.
弗兰克 祝你好运
Good luck, Frank.
"底特律西区警察局"
谋杀未遂?他不想杀人
Attempted murder? It's not like he killed someone.
这妨碍了我当事人的人身权利
This violates my client's civil rights.
把指控改为殴打 我现在就可以用现金把他保释出来
Make it assault and I can make bail in cash, now.
听着 你的当事人是个卑鄙小人 你也是个卑鄙小人
Listen, your client's a scumbag, you're a scumbag...
星期一早晨去和法官谈吧
...and scumbags see the judge.
和这个可笑的家伙一起滚出警察局
Now get out of my police station and take Laughing Boy with you.
嗨
Hi.
墨菲 从南区调来
Murphy, transferring in from Metro South.
好地方
Nice precinct.
是的 不错的地方
Yeah, pretty good.
开始工作
You work for a living down here.
去换上制服吧
Get your armor and suit up.
-不 你不能喝咖啡 -哦 警官
- No, you can't get a cup of coffee. - Oh, sarge.
-斯塔克 有弗莱德瑞克森的消息吗? -还是没有脱离危险
- Stark, any word on Frederickson? - Still listed as critical.
他老婆一定疯了
His wife must be going crazy.
-墨菲? -嗯 我就是
- Murphy? - Yeah, that's me.
-我叫曼森 -嗨
- Manson. - Hi.
谁让你来这鬼地方的?
What brings you to paradise?
全销公司调来了很多人
I think the OCP's moving a lot of new guys here.
全销公司里全是笨蛋
Omni Consumer Products. What a bunch of morons.
他们会把警察局弄垮的
They're gonna manage this department right into the ground.
-从哪来? -南区
- Where you from? - Metro South.
欢迎来到地狱
Welcome to hell.
-墨菲? -哦
- Murphy? - Yo.
-他们在城东杀了十个人 -情况紧急找不到支援
- Cut 10 guys loose on the east side. - Try to get up when you're in a jam.
是呀 受了伤再找医生
Try to get a Medevac after you been jammed.
我来告诉你我们该做什么 我们应该罢工
I'll tell you what we should do. We should strike.
明天举行葬礼
The funeral is tomorrow.
每个休假的警员都要参加
Department requests all officers not on duty to attend.
慰问金和平常一样交给塞西尔
Any donations for the family may be given to Cecil as usual.
我不想再听到任何人谈论罢工
I don't want to hear any more talk about strike.
我们不是水管工 我们是警察
We're not plumbers, we're police officers.
警察是不会罢工的
And police officers don't strike.
墨菲 出来一下
Murphy. Front and center.
哦 警察!
Ooh, tiger!
露易丝 把嫌疑犯归案后过来一下
Lewis, come here when you're finished fucking around with your suspect.
他是你的新搭档
This guy's gonna be your new partner.
墨菲 来见见露易丝 带他看看周围的环境
Murphy, meet Lewis. Show him the neighborhood.
很高兴认识你 墨菲
Glad to know you, Murphy.
身手不错
Pretty neat.
你对环境不熟悉 还是我来开吧
I better drive until you know your way around.
带新搭档时通常是我开车
I usually drive when I'm breaking in a new partner.
你真的认为那个老家伙会来?
You really think the old man will be there?
为什么叫我们去?
Why invite us?
所有的部门主管都来了 这是个重要的会议
All the division heads are bringing their support teams. It's big.
他们要通过三角新城计划
They're green lighting Delta City.
才不会呢 他们总是拖拖拉拉
No way. They never move ahead of schedule.
琼斯已经完成了209系列 而且想展示一下
Jones has the 209 series ready and wants to show off.
-真是一波三折 鲍勃 -什么?
- Tough break, Bob. - What?
ED 209计划受阻时
When ED 209 ran into serious delays...
老家伙需要另一个备用计划
...the old man ordered a backup plan.
95楼到了 祝您幸运
95th floor, have a nice day.
或许这么做是用来催促一下琼斯
Probably to light a fire under Jones' ass.
-是呀 -鲍勃接到了这个任务
- Yeah. - Old Bob here gets the assignment.
但没人把这个备用计划当回事
Nobody in Security Concepts takes it seriously.
去他的琼斯 我有事会直接去找老家伙
Fucking Jones, I'd go straight to the old man if I could.
别和琼斯纠缠
Don't mess with Jones.
小心点 我听说琼斯不是好惹的
Be careful, man. I hear Jones is a real shark.
-别再说了 好吗? -鲍勃
- Who asked you, twerp? - Bob.
警察最近是怎么了?
What's the problem with the police?
我们接管后 工会一直在抱怨 这很正常
Their union's been bitching ever since we took over. The usual stuff.
我们会处理好的
But we'll turn things around.
好 非常好 我们开始吧
Good. Very good. Let's get started.
朋友们
My friends.
这是我10多年来的一个梦想
I've had this dream for more than a decade now.
请大家和我一起分享
A dream which I've invited you all to share with me.
6个月后 我们会开始建造
In six months we begin construction...
三角新城
...of Delta City.
它将建在底特律旧城区上
Where Old Detroit now stands.
底特律旧城区有一个顽症
Old Detroit has a cancer.
这个顽症就是犯罪
The cancer is crime.
除掉这个顽症 我们才能雇用两百万名工人
It must be cut out before we employ the 2 million...
开始建造新城
...workers to breathe life back into the city.
说得真好
Yes.
革新的税法会使经济前景光明
Shifts in tax structure have made the economy ideal for corporate growth.
但是在治安状况恶劣的情况下 社区服务
But community services, in this case law enforcement...
前景令人堪忧
...have suffered.
是我们出击的时候了
I think it's time we gave something back.
细细看看公司的历史
Take a close look at the track record of this company.
你会发现我们
You'll see that we've gambled...
在似乎无利可图的市场投机
...in markets usually regarded as nonprofit.
医院、监狱、空间勘探
Hospitals. Prisons. Space exploration.
好生意是不会送上门的
I say, good business is where you find it.
大家都知道 我们签约运作本市的警察
As you know, we now have a contract to run local law enforcement.
但是
But at Security Concepts...
我们认为高效率的警察只是解决问题的一个方面
...we believe an efficient police force is only part of the solution.
不止这些 我们还需要更多的
No, we need something more.
我们要一个24小时制的警员
We need a 24-hour-a-day police officer.
不要吃饭也不要睡觉
A cop who doesn't need to eat or sleep.
强大的火力、良好的机动性能
A cop with superior firepower and the reflexes to use it.
各位部门主管
Fellow executives...
很荣幸为您介绍法律执行的未来
...it's a pleasure to introduce you to the future of law enforcement.
ED 209
ED 209.
执法者系列209型
The Enforcement Droid series 209...
是全自动的机械警察
...is a self-sufficient law enforcement robot.
209型现在是被用来进行市内执法
209 is programmed for urban pacification, but that's just a start.
但在底特律旧城区成功使用后
After a successful tour in Old Detroit...
我们预计209型将成为未来热门的军事产品
...we can expect 209 to become the hot military product for the next decade.
-麦克纳马拉博士 -我们需要一个拘捕对象
- Dr. McNamara. - We'll need a subject.
-肯尼先生 -是的 先生
- Mr. Kinney. - Yes, sir.
-能帮个忙吗? -好的 先生
- Will you give us a hand? - Yes, sir.
肯尼先生将会帮助我们演示一个典型的缴械行动
Mr. Kinney will help us simulate a typical arrest and disarming procedure.
肯尼先生 用枪进行恐吓
Mr. Kinney, use your gun in a threatening manner.
-用枪指着ED 209 -是的 先生
- Point it at ED 209. - Yes, sir.
限你在二十秒内
Please put down your weapon.
放下武器
You have 20 seconds to comply.
我想你最好照它说的做
I think you better do what he says.
现在还有十五秒
You now have 15 seconds to comply.
你违反刑法第九款第十三条
You are in direct violation of penal code 113, section 9.
-还有五秒 -救命!
- You have five seconds to comply. - Help me!
-四 三 二 一 -救命!救命!
- Four, three, two, one. - Help me! Help!
我现在被授权使用武力
I am now authorized to use physical force.
还不快去叫救护车?
Somebody want to call a paramedic?
-快去 约翰逊 -谁来把开关关了?
- Let's go, Johnson. - You pull the plug on this thing?
好的 别碰它
All right, don't touch him.
-别碰! -它没有听到枪落地的声音
- Don't touch him! - He didn't hear the gun drop.
它没听到?
He didn't hear it?!
我对你太失望了 迪克
Dick, I'm very disappointed.
只是个小故障 暂时受挫
It's only a glitch. A temporary setback.
你认为这是小故障?
You call this a glitch?
原计划半年后投产
We're to begin construction in six months.
"暂时受挫"会损失几百万利息
This setback could cost us millions in interest costs alone.
不一定
Not necessarily, sir.
我的机械战警计划
There's a Robocop program...
就是针对这种情况的后备计划
...I developed as a contingency against just this sort of thing.
谢谢你的关心
Thank you for your concern.
-我们应该...... -等一下 迪克!
- This is something we could... - Wait a minute. Dick!
或许我们该有新的观点
Maybe what we need here is a fresh perspective.
莫顿先生 把你的计划告诉我 要花多长时间?
Tell me about your plan. How long will it take?
我已将警察部门优化组合
We've restructured the police department with some good candidates.
九十天内就可以推出原型机
We can go to prototype within 90 days.
非常好
Very good.
把你的资料整理一下 过二十分钟来见我
Get your staff together. I'll expect a presentation in 20 minutes.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
我们伺机而动 这就是竞争
That's how it is in the big leagues. You see an opening, you go for it.
小心点 琼斯会对付你的
Watch your back, Jones will be looking for you.
去他的 他弄糟了 我是来收拾残局的
Fuck Jones. He fumbled the ball and I was there to pick it up.
肯尼死了真可惜 不是吗?
Too bad about Kinney, huh?
这就是命运
That's life in the big city.
计划何时开始?
When do we start?
就等那些笨蛋志愿者了
As soon as some schmuck volunteers.
墨菲 你的动作好棒
Pretty fancy moves, Murphy.
我儿子看了TJ雷泽的电视
My son watches this cop show, TJ Lazer.
雷泽在杀了坏人后就做这样的动作
Lazer does this whenever he kills a bad guy.
-他认每个出色的警察...... -而你不想让他失望
- My kid thinks every good cop... - You don't want to disappoint him.
应该为孩子树立好榜样
Yeah, well, role models can be very important to a boy.
说实话 我也喜欢这样
Okay, I get a kick out of it.
所有单位注意、所有单位注意 在第九区
All units, sector nine...
这是......
Well, that's...
为什么你不开?
Why don't you drive?
见鬼!
Shit!
-我真不敢相信! -怎么了?
- I don't believe it! - What?
你把钱全烧了!
You burnt the fucking money!
可我要把门炸开!你还想怎么样?
I had to blow the door!
笨蛋 钱上有记号
It's as good as marked, asshole.
你这个超级大笨蛋!
You stupid, stupid asshole!
-克拉伦斯! -干什么?
- Clarence! - What do you want?!
有警察跟在后面
We got a cop on our tail.
-快点加速 -快开!
- Come on, speed it up. - Move it!
-我们跑不过警察的 -减速
- We ain't gonna outrun a cop. - Slow down.
-你疯了吗? -闭嘴 照做吧!
- Are you crazy? - Shut the fuck up and do it!
快减速!
Just do it!
我是154 我们在追踪嫌疑犯 请求支援
This is 154. We're in pursuit of suspect. Request backup.
-收到 154 现在没有支援 -把你的枪给我
- Roger, 154. Backup unavailable. - Give me your piece.
估计支援十五分钟后到达
Backup ETA, 15 minutes.
鲍勃 到车门那去!
Bobby, get the door!
-大家都上好膛! -大家快点
- Everybody load up! - Let's go, come on.
-好的 -好的 开始
- Okay. - All right, here we go.
-怎么回事? -他去哪了?
- What the fuck? - Where'd he go?
埃米尔!
Emil!
他在那!
He's up here!
杀了他!
Get him!
见鬼 克拉伦斯 我的腿受伤了
Shit, Clarence, my leg.
里昂 把他抬起来
Leon, pick him up.
-准备好了吗? -等一下
- Ready? - Nope, hang on.
鲍勃
Bobby.
-鲍勃 你会飞吗? -不 克拉伦斯!
- Can you fly, Bobby? - Clarence, no!
撞上了!
Hit it!
这是154 我们在D区追踪那辆货车 支援来了吗?
This is 154. We've located that van in sector 3D. Where's backup?
没有支援 估计二十分钟后到达
Backup unavailable. Estimate 20 minutes before units can arrive.
你来呼叫试试
Well, you call it.
-先行动吧 -好的
- Let's's do it. - Okay.
走
Go.
保持联络
Stay in touch.
不许动
Freeze.
好的 把手举起来
Okay, let's see those hands.
慢慢的
Nice and easy.
该死
Sure.
介意我拉上拉链吗?
Mind if I zip this up?
我们抢银行 但是没有余钱
We rob banks, but never get to keep the money.
我们用偷来的钱买毒品 然后再倒卖来赚钱
We steal money to buy coke, then sell the coke to make more money.
-这是投资 -要那么麻烦吗?只管抢钱就可以了
- Capital investment, man. - Why bother? We could just steal it.
这比抢钱强多了
No better way to steal than free enterprise.
抽烟吗?
Smoke?
不 这东西会要你的命
No, those things will kill you.
你想长生不老?
You want to live forever?
不许动
Don't move.
开枪吧
Go ahead and do it.
不论你死还是活 我都要带你走
Dead or alive, you're coming with me.
露易丝?
Lewis ?
露易丝!
这里有情况
I got a situation in here.
给我起来 起来!
Okay, tough guy, get up. Get up!
转过身子 把腿张开 怎么样
Turn around and spread your legs. That's right.
露易丝 你在哪?你怎么样?
Lewis, where are you? You all right?
把手放到头上
Hands on your head.
露易丝
Lewis.
埃米尔 让我们来
Let us take over from here, Emil.
你的小命在我手里了
Your ass is mine.
不!
No!
还没有
Not yet, it ain't.
看看是谁来了?
Well, what have we here?
你是个棒警察?
You a good cop, hotshot?
你一定是个棒警察
Sure you are.
你是那种不一般的警察
You gotta be some kind of great cop.
敢只身闯虎穴
Come in here all by yourself.
你的搭档呢?
Where's your partner?
你的搭档在哪?
还有一个在楼上
Guys, the other one was upstairs.
是个女的
She was sweet.
我杀了她
I took her out.
你一定很生气
I bet that really pisses you off.
你不认为我是个好人吧
You probably don't think I'm a very nice guy.
不是吗?
Do you?
你是个无赖
I think you're slime.
这有个问题
See, I got this problem.
警察不喜欢我
Cops don't like me.
所以我也不喜欢警察
So I don't like cops.
帮他一把
Well, give the man a hand.
我把他交给你们了
He's all yours.
-小心 -转过来
- Look out. - Turn around, man.
嗨 好孩子 嗨 来这儿
Hey, pretty boy. Hey, over here.
我没子弹了
I'm out of ammo.
我也是
Me too.
克拉伦斯!他还活着
Hey, Clarence! He is still alive
疼不疼?疼不疼?
Does it hurt? Does it hurt?
玩够了
Okay, fun's over.
离开这儿
Okay, let's get out of here.
晚安 甜心王子
Good night, sweet prince.
等等我 等等我
Hey, wait up. Wait up.
墨菲
Murphy.
-把他抬过来 -明白
- Get him over. - Clear.
给他戴上氧气罩 让他呼吸起来
Ventilate him. Get the mask.
把门打开
Okay, hit the door.
-我来量血压 -给他戴上氧气罩
- Let me get pressure. - Mask him.
血压六十
Got a pressure of 60 pel.
把管子插进去
We're gonna have to intubate this guy.
我插好了 开始呼吸了吗?
All right, I got it in. Breath sounds?
-已经进去了 -现在插另一边的
- You're in. - Other side.
-准备好面罩吸氧 -把衣服脱下来
- Let's get the mask trousers up. - Get the clothes off.
脱下来了 准备一级救护
Clothes off. Prep him for a central line.
抽取血样 交叉配型实验 六个单位
Let's get some blood drawn. Type and crossing, six units.
血压在下降
Pressure's dropping.
一级救护 把压板拿来 注射普通盐水
Central line's in, getting pressure back. Normal saline.
爸爸 你能做出这样的动作吗?
Can you do that, Dad?
-我有事要告诉你 -血压多少?
- I really have to tell you something. - Blood pressure?
-我抽了四十培尔 -好的
- I've got 40 pel. - All right.
开始电击
Coarse D-fib. Okay, we gotta shock him.
留置福利导尿管 我们要持续氧流量
Put the Foley in. Let's blow the mask trousers.
-好的 -站开
- Okay. - Stand clear.
再来一次
Coarse D-fib. Let's shock him again.
明白
Clear.
心电图还是平的 注射肾上腺素
Flat line. Let's go, intracardiac epinephrine.
-注射完毕 -还是没有脉搏
- All right, it's in. - No pulse.
再来最后一次电击
Let's go ahead and shock a flat line and then quit.
-大家都站开 -明白
- Okay, everybody stand clear. - Clear.
我们已经尽力了 喊他们过来
All right, that's all we can do. Let's call it.
什么时候死亡的?
What's the time?
六点十五
6:15.
清楚了
Sharp.
又抖动了
It's starting to roll.
见鬼!
Shit!
把电路管拿来
Bring in the L.E.D.
把它安装好
Lock it down.
-他已经启动了 -怎么样?
- He's on. - What's the story?
-我们保住了他的左臂 -什么?
- We saved the left arm. - What?
我们是商量好了全身再造的 扔掉手臂
We agreed on total body prosthesis. Now lose the arm.
我的老天
Jesus, Morton.
-他知道我在说什么吗? -没关系 我们会清除他的记忆
- Can he understand? - We'll blank his memory, anyway.
我们应该丢弃掉手臂 你怎么看?
We should lose the arm. What do you think?
他曾在加入警队时签过协议 他已经死了
He signed a release when he joined the force. And he's dead.
我们可以随意处置
We can do pretty much what we want.
扔掉手臂
Lose the arm.
把他关上 准备做手术
Shut him down. Prep him for surgery.
外壳会是这样的
The outer skin will be like this.
凯夫拉装甲外面镀一层钛
It's titanium, laminated with Kevlar.
去和他握手
Go ahead, shake his hand.
常来吗?过得好吗?
Come here often? How you doing?
手劲真不小
Got a hell of a grip.
他有四百磅的力量
It's 400 foot-pounds.
他可以把你的手上的每块骨头捏碎
He could crush every bone in your hand.
好的 接到肩膀上
All right, attach it to his shoulder.
我喜欢这样
I like that.
你会成为威力无穷的机器人!
You're gonna be a bad motherfucker!
嗨 嗨 看 他在看我们!
Hey, hey. Look, he's watching us!
这是给你的
This is for you.
新年快乐
Happy New Year.
我们使用了世界上做先进的科技
We get the best of both worlds.
它拥有当今最先进的应用技术
The fastest reflexes possible today...
通过电脑存储信息
...computer-assisted memory...
拥有终生巡逻的程序
...and a lifetime of on-the-street officer programming.
很荣幸向大家介绍
It is my great pleasure to present to you...
机械战警
...Robocop.
过来 过来
Come on, come on.
是在为你鼓掌
That's for you.
-是在为你鼓掌 -去吧
- That's for you. - Go, Robo.
我就是你说的惯犯
I'm what you call a repeat offender.
我还会再犯罪的
I will offend again.
我会变本加厉的
I get my orders from a higher source.
闭嘴 笨蛋
Shut up, asshole.
-从这边走 -这儿有一个观察室
- Go through the side. - A cell is set for observation.
这是怎么回事?
What's this all about?
-这是谁? -约翰瑞德士官
- Who's this? - Sergeant John Reed.
这是OCP官方事宜 请让开
It's official OCP business, so please, get lost.
-我们要花四到五天...... -胡说!
- We got four or five days... - Hey, this is bullshit!
我只接受......
I take my orders from...
这是什么鬼东西?
What is this shit?
要休息的时候 就坐在椅子上
When at rest, you'll sit in a chair.
是的 我明白
Yes, I understand.
追踪仪呢?
What about tracking?
用这个可以查找他所在的方位
We check his exact location with one of these.
他吃什么东西?
How does he eat?
他的消化系统很简单
His digestive system is simple.
这个处理器制造的糊状物质维持它的机能
This processor dispenses a paste that sustains his organic systems.
吃起来像婴儿食品
It tastes like baby food
随便你吃
Knock yourself out.
-现在开始追踪 -给我一个座标方格
- Let's start with tracking. - Give me a grid.
-明白吗? -明白
- Got it? - Clear.
-定位 -核对无误
- Target. - Check.
开始追踪
Now follow.
核对无误
Check.
语音分析
Voice stress analyzer.
-开始 -一 二
- It's up. - One, two...
三
...three.
-核对无误 -记录
- Check. - Record.
-先再回放 -回放一半
- Now playback. - Bring it up 50%.
给个全景
Full frame.
我想他已经准备好了
I think he's ready.
-成功了 -好了 我来
- We got it. - All right, clear out.
你的行为准则是什么?
What are your prime directives?
服务大众
Serve the public trust.
保护无辜 维护法律
Protect the innocent. Uphold the law.
行为准则 1:服务大众 2:保护无辜 3:维护法律
Serve the public trust.Protect the innocent. Uphold the law.
不错
That's good.
真不错
That's very good.
准则4:机密
我喜欢上这家伙了
I fucking love that guy.
-这是超级警察 -看那把枪
- It's Supercop. - Look at that fucking gun.
我的天!
Shit!
-这人真棒 -他不是人 是一个机器
- This guy is good. - He's not a guy, he's a machine.
他们想干什么?取代我们?
What are they gonna do? Replace us?
过来
Come on.
-瑞德 -是
- Reed. - Yeah.
他要辆车
He needs a car.
谢谢
Thank you.
别客气
Sure.
随时恭候
Anytime.
很好 去吧
Oh, yeah. Go get 'em, boy.
我要用一美元买个美女
I'd buy that for a dollar.
来猜猜下面我要干什么?
And guess what I'm going to do now?
毕克斯比 祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday, Bixby.
您还要什么?
Is there anything else, sir?
把收银机里的钱全放到袋子里
Empty the register and put the money in the bag.
我没听清?
Excuse me?
我说把你的钱全给我 别和我兜圈子!
I said, give me your money, all of it, and don't fuck with me!
快点!
Now move!
打开保险柜
Open the safe, pops.
打开那该死的保险柜!
Open the goddamn safe!
-我们没有保险柜 -妈的
- We don't have a safe. - Shit.
这是你们那该死的保险柜!现在打开那鬼东西
There's your goddamned safe! Now open the son of a bitch.
-别发火 -打开那鬼东西!
Quit stalling. You better open that son of a bitch!
快点!
Come on!
我会杀了她的
I'm gonna blow her brains out.
-我会打开保险柜的 -就这样
- I'll open the safe. - Good boy.
我数三下之内 你就要打开 一 二......
You better open that on the count of three. One, two...
去你的
Fuck me.
放下武器 你被捕了
Drop the gun. You are under arrest.
去你的!
Fuck me! Fuck me! Fuck me!
谢谢您的合作 晚安
Thank you for your cooperation. Good night.
我要花一元买个美女!
I'll buy that for a dollar!
三号街／纳什大道 415正前往
不 别这样!
No, please!
别碰我!
Don't touch me!
-让开!让开! -我们不想要你的钱!
- Get away! Get away! - We don't want your money!
放松点 我们不会伤害你的
Take it easy. We don't want to hurt you.
你的头发太多了
Too much hair.
我明白了!我们要给她剪头
I know! We'll give her a haircut.
-嗨 嗨! -什么?
- Hey, hey! - What?
下面的头发更多!
There's more hair down there!
不!别这样!
No! Don't!
求求你们
Please.
放了那个女的 你们被捕了
Let the woman go. You are under arrest.
见鬼
Shit.
你最好退后 他会伤到她的!
You better back up, pal, because he's gonna do her!
他会杀了她的!
He's gonna kill her!
定位 准则2:保护无辜
他会杀了她的!
He's gonna kill her!
该轮到你了
Your move, creep.
没问题 我照做
No problem. It's okay.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
吓死我了 谢谢你
I was so scared. Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
夫人 你精神受刺激了
Madam, you have suffered an emotional shock.
我会通知强暴救助中心的
I will notify a rape crisis center.
各单位注意 第六区 到十字路口集合
All units, sector six. Please close intersections...
我不在乎 现在把人都赶到楼梯旁边去
I don't care. Get those men by the stairs, now.
市政局里从未发生过恐怖事件
Terrorism has never been a factor in city politics before.
但今天前市议员
That changed today when former councilman...
罗纳德·米勒持枪闯入市政大厅
...Ron Miller entered City Hall with a gun.
他现在在二楼
He's on the second floor...
挟持吉布森市长及其随从作为人质
...holding Mayor Gibson and his staff hostage.
有证据指出米勒已杀死一名人质
We do believe that Miller has killed one of the hostages.
-下一步怎么办 中尉? -静观其变 恐怖行动很棘手
- Lieutenant, what's next? - We wait. Terrorism is very tricky.
最好给他来个出其不意 不巧的是......
Massive and immediate retaliation is the best policy. Unfortunately...
-对不起 -等一下 你去哪?
- Excuse us. - Wait, where you going?
请说一下情况
Statement, please.
嗨 这儿人太多了 快让这些人靠后!
Hey, let's have some crowd control. Come on, get these people back!
-你要去哪? -保持和他对话
- Where the hell are you going? - Keep him talking.
只有一个问题!
One quick question here!
谁制造了你?
Who made you?
你是所向无敌的吗?
Are you invincible?
好的 米勒 别伤害市长
Okay, Miller. Don't hurt the mayor.
我们会给你任何你想要的东西
We'll give you whatever you want.
首先 别骗我
First, don't fuck with me.
我是亡命之徒
I'm a desperate man.
然后 我要新鲜的煮咖啡
And second, I want some fresh coffee.
第三 我要重新唱票
And third, I want a recount.
不论结果如何 我要维持原来的职位
No matter how it turns out, I want my old job back.
-好的 -我还想要间更大的办公室
- Okay. - And I want a bigger office.
我还要辆新车!由市政府全额付款!
And I want a new car! And I want the city to pay for it all!
-米勒 你想要什么样的车? -有能向后倾倒的真皮座位
- What kind of car, Miller? - One with reclining leather seats...
速度快、耗油量大
...that goes really fast and gets really shitty gas mileage.
6000 SUX怎么样?
How about the 6000 SUX?
好的
Yeah.
当然可以
Okay, sure.
有自动巡航仪吗?车子有自动巡航仪吗?
What about cruise control? Does it have cruise control?
没问题 米勒
No problem, Miller.
放市长走 我们什么都好谈
Let the mayor go, we'll even throw in a Blaupunkt.
你别骗我 中尉!
Lieutenant, don't jerk me off!
你别骗我 不然我杀了你!
When people jerk me off, I kill them!
想看看吗?
You want to see?
热成像
起来 站起来!
Get up, Your Honor. Get up!
站起来 大家想见见你
Get up. Your public wants to see you.
热成像
谁也不把我当回事!
Nobody ever takes me seriously!
现在你们要刮目相看了
We'll get serious now...
和市长永别吧!
...and kiss the mayor's ass goodbye!
机械战警 他是谁?他是什么?
Robocop. Who is he? What is he?
他是从哪来的?
Where does he come from?
它是OCP在严打中
He is OCP's newest soldier...
使用的最新装备
...in their revolutionary crime management program.
OCP发言人声明这部令人生畏的机器
OCP spokesmen claim the fearless machine...
改变了底特律旧城区的治安状况
...has crooks on the run in Old Detroit.
今天 李艾科卡小学的学生亲眼看见了
Today, kids at Lee lacocca Elementary got to meet in person...
他们父母只在漫画书上看到的东西
...what their parents only read about in comic books.
请问机械战警
Excuse me, Robo...
对在家的孩子们有什么忠告?
...any special message for all the kids watching at home?
别出门惹麻烦
Stay out of trouble.
今天墨西哥发生了更多的冲突
More fighting in the Mexican crisis...
美军和墨西哥政府军在阿卡普尔科一起
...when American troops joined in a raid with Mexican Nationals...
搜寻反政府武装的火箭基地
...against rebel rocket positions in Acapulco.
稍后再见
Now this.
红色警报!红色警报!
Red alert. Red alert.
你越过了警戒线
You crossed my line of death.
你没有拆除你的导弹
You haven't dismantled your MX stockpile.
巴基斯坦威胁到我领土的安全了!
Pakistan is threatening my border!
就这么多了 没有后勤援助了
That's it, buster. No more military aid.
原子战
Nukem.
讲的是先发制人
Get them before they get you.
巴特勒兄弟公司出品的 又一款高品质家用游戏:毁灭
Another quality home game from Butler Brothers.
今天工会领导人同意建造OCP的三角新城
Today labor leaders agreed to sanction construction of OCP's Delta City...
从而创造了一百万个就业机会
...thereby creating one million much-needed new jobs...
但工人在底特律旧城区的安全问题还没得到解决
...despite questions about worker safety in dangerous Old Detroit.
OCP保安副总裁罗伯特·莫顿接受了采访
Robert Morton, vice president, Security Concepts, OCP.
我不对三角城区作评论 但我可以告诉大家
I can't comment on Delta City. But I will tell you this:
四十天内底特律旧城区的犯罪将会销声匿迹
Security Concepts projects the end of crime in Old Detroit within 40 days.
这是因为新出现的机械战警
There's a new guy in town. His name's Robocop.
嗨 嗨 嗨 副总裁 祝贺你
Hey, hey, hey, Bobby-boy. Vice president. Congratulations.
-周二晚上有时间打手球吗? -我很想去 比尔
- Handball Tuesday night? - I would, Bill...
但是有模特来我家
...but I've got some models coming to my place.
我用一元买美女
I'd buy that for a dollar.
请进
Welcome to the club, Bob.
机械战警让你炙手可热
You're making a name for yourself in Security Concepts with Robocop.
我没想到
I try.
我们尽力而为
Let me in on the bottom line, pal.
听说琼斯中尉很生气
I hear Jones was plenty pissed.
你知道 他只是个纸老虎
You know, he's got this killer rep, but it's a smoke screen.
他已经失势了 不堪一击
He's lost his teeth. The guy's a pussy.
我们是在说同一个迪克·琼斯吗?
Are we talking about the same Dick Jones?
长江后浪推前浪 这就是生活
He's old, we're young. That's life.
我有个会议先走了
I gotta go. I got a meeting.
恭喜你 鲍勃
Congratulations, Bob.
谢谢
Thanks.
当我是这个公司年轻的行政人员时
I remember when I was a young executive at this company.
我们也为他们起外号
We used to call the old man funny names.
"老脸皮厚"
"Iron Butt."
"蠢驴"
"Boner."
我甚至叫他
Once I even called him...
"老不中用"
..."asshole."
但是我对他仍很尊敬
But there was always respect.
我是有限度的
I always knew where the line was drawn.
但你过了火
And you just stepped over it, buddy-boy.
你侮辱了我
You've insulted me.
你造出来的那玩意侮辱了公司
And you've insulted this company with your bastard creation.
我可以保证执法者209型的军火销售
I had a guaranteed military sale with ED 209.
及其更新计划
Renovation program.
它的零件可以销售25年
Spare parts for 25 years.
谁管它有没有用呢?
Who cares if it worked or not?
老家伙的意见很重要 迪克
The old man thought it was pretty important, Dick.
你知道
You know...
他是一个好老头
...he's a sweet old man.
而且光明磊落
And he means well.
但他不会长生不老
But he's not gonna live forever.
我也是这里的二把手
And I'm number two around here.
这么简单的道理你也不懂?
Pretty simple math, huh, Bob?
你
ou just...
看错人了
...fucked with the wrong guy.
你疯了
You're out of your fucking mind.
你最好祈祷
You better pray...
别遇上麻烦
...that that unholy monster of yours doesn't screw up.
饿了吗?
You hungry?
不 谢谢
No, thanks.
哦 不
Oh, no.
该死的暴徒炸了墨西哥的一个机场
Damn rebels blew up the airport in Acapulco.
真不错 我们下周正准备去那 嗨 这是什么?
Great, we were going there next week. Hey, what was that?
嗨 你看
Hey, look.
他启动了
Bucket-boy's online.
嗨 嗨!
Hey. Hey!
站住 停下!
Halt. Stop!
等一下!
Wait a minute!
-怎么回事? -我不知道 他只是离开了这儿
- What's going on? - I don't know. He just left.
他只是离开了这儿?
He just left?
罗斯福!
Roosevelt !
有麻烦了
We got a problem.
让一下
Out of the way.
看看这个
Take a look at this.
见鬼!快叫鲍勃·莫顿
Shit! Call Bob Morton.
杰尔 你把他归案 我一会儿就来
Jerry, book him. I'll catch up with you later.
你好
Hello.
我来自我介绍一下
I haven't really had a chance to introduce myself.
我是安妮·露易丝
I'm Anne Lewis.
你有名字吗?
Do you have a name?
你有什么事 露易丝警员?
How can I help you, Officer Lewis?
我不是那个意思
That's not really what I meant.
你没有名字吗?
Don't you have a name?
别让他走 在这儿签个名
Hold it. Sign right here.
你搞错了 我是OCP生产出来的
You don't understand. I'm OCP.
你是......
Murphy.
墨菲
It's you.
你真把我忘了?
You really don't remember me?
对不起
Excuse me.
我得走了
I have to go.
有案子发生了
Somewhere, there is a crime happening.
站住!
Stop !
-你和他说了什么? -没什么
- What did you talk to him about? - Nothing.
-见鬼 -见鬼
- Shit. - Shit.
站住!
Stop !
嗨 呆在那儿!站住!
Hey, you there! Stop!
你有大麻烦了
You're in a lot of trouble, officer.
过来
Come on.
你们曾向我保证过会通力合作的
I was assured full cooperation by this precinct.
如果把事情弄糟了 我就炒你的鱿鱼!
One of your grunts screws it up, I'll have your job!
-有什么新情况? -还不是很清楚
- What's the update? - Hard to know.
是小毛病还是其他什么?
We have a glitch or what?
设计时没考虑到它休息时的问题
He wasn't designed for somatic rest.
他做了一个梦 一个梦
He had a dream. A dream.
这个警察盘问了她
This cop questioned him.
我没有盘问他 我只是问他的名字 他不知道
I didn't question him. I asked his name. He didn't know.
哦 真好
Oh, great.
我来澄清一下 它没有名字 只有程序
Let me make it clear. He doesn't have a name, he has a program.
它是一个产品
He's product.
-明白了吗? -当然
- Is that clear? - Sure.
把他找回来 做个系统检测
Pull him in. Run a systems check, the works.
因为做了个梦就把他撤下来?
Take him offline because he had a dream?
你在开玩笑吧?
What, are you kidding?
我们离开这儿
Let's get out of here.
听着 瑞德
Listen, Reed.
你要记住一件事:
Try to keep one thing in mind:
这个计划和警察无关 这属于机密
This project doesn't concern cops. It's classified.
这是OCP的事 先生 你明白吗?
It's OCP. You got it, mister?
是的 我知道了
Yeah, I got it
好的
Good.
对不起 警官
Sorry, sarge.
我弄糟了
I fucked up.
别放在心上 孩子 这家伙是个大混蛋
Forget it, kid. This guy's a serious asshole.
书呆子 把钱都给我 不然我杀了你
Give me all your money, bookworm, or I blow your brains out.
注满七号油箱
Now fill it up on number seven.
别做蠢事 老兄
Don't do nothing stupid, man.
我的枪法不错
I'm a good shot.
我能从这打中你
I can hit you from here.
发生案件
嗨 老兄
Hey, man...
你在看什么书?
...what you reading in there?
《宇宙地理》
你是大学生?
You a college boy or something?
你一定认为自己很聪明 你认为你能比过子弹吗?
I'll bet you think you're smart. Think you could outsmart a bullet?
我们来试试看 怎么样?
What do you say we find out, huh?
我在和你说话!你觉得怎么样?
I'm talking to you! What do you say, huh?
我在和你说话!
I'm talking to you!
放下武器
Drop it.
不论你死还是活 我都要带你走
Dead or alive, you are coming with me.
我认识你
I know you.
你死了
You're dead.
记录
我们杀了你
We killed you.
录像
我们杀了你
We killed you.
我们杀了你!
回放
我们杀了你
We killed you.
你是谁?
Who are you?
能为您效劳吗 先生?
Can I help you, sir?
不用
No.
你到底想要什么?
What is it exactly that you want?
嗨
Hey,
你不能进这里
You can't enter here.
等一下 嗨 等一下
Wait a second. Hey, just a minute.
这里是禁区
This is a restricted area.
已进入系统
He's in.
底特律警察局 刑事犯罪科
按照片检索
请输入数据
正在输入
比对
吻合
安东诺斯基·埃米尔·M
已知同伙
纳什·里昂·C
克斯·乔·P
明·史蒂夫
克拉伦斯·伯蒂迪克
刑事犯罪
拘捕记录
涉嫌杀害墨菲
你是墨菲
Murphy, it's you.
涉嫌杀害墨菲
墨菲·艾里克斯·J
已死亡
樱草路548号
樱草路
待售
欢迎你 让我们一起来参观你的新居
Welcome, shopper. Let's take a stroll through your new home.
这是由ZM工业建造的家庭房屋
This is a one-family house built by ZM Industries.
靠近学校和商店
Situated near schools and shops...
每年增值百分之七
...this progressive development has a growth factor of seven.
哇
Wow.
爸爸 你能做出这样的动作吗?
Can you do that, Dad?
谁来烧饭并不重要
Say, it doesn't matter who cooks in your family...
因为厨房由专家设计
...because this kitchen by Food Concepts...
做饭很容易
...makes everything a snap.
爸爸
Dad.
快戴上帽子 他看不可爱吗?
Come on, get your hat on. Isn't he cute?
爸爸快来 爸爸快来
Come on, Dad. Come on, Dad.
我有事要告诉你
I really have to tell you something.
我爱你
I love you.
这是主卧室
The master bedroom.
格调优雅的分区设计
Functional space with a touch of elegance.
嗨 您考虑好了吗?开个价吧?
Hey, have you thought it all over? Why not make me an offer?
拘捕模式
拘捕模式 嫌疑犯:纳什·里昂
克拉伦斯·伯蒂迪克在哪?
Where is Clarence Boddicker?
好的
Okay.
-妈的 -我们来谈谈
- Shit. - Let's talk.
狗娘养的!
Son of a bitch!
这头衔听起来真不错
There's just something about the way it sounds:
"副总裁"
"Vice president."
我已经动情了
It just turns me on.
老天 你们真是太棒了
God, you girls are so great.
我喜欢聪明的女孩子
I love to be with intelligent women.
聪明让你更性感
Smart is so sexy.
我知道
I know.
有时 我一想起一些事
Sometimes, I could just think of something...
就让我兴奋
...and it could just get me so horny.
是的 好点子浪费了真可惜
Yeah, well, a mind is a terrible thing to waste.
我很容易就厌烦
I get bored so easily.
你需要一些彩排 鲍勃
And you need lots of stimulation, Bobby.
是的 我来了
Yes, I do.
-别动 -我不会的
- Don't move. - I won't.
鲍勃 别忘了我
Bob, save some for me.
别担心
Don't worry.
一定是送香槟 我去
Must be the champagne. Stay here.
好了吗?
How you doing?
臭女人 快滚
Bitches, leave.
再见 鲍勃
Gee, Bobby. Bye.
别忘了给我打电话?
You gonna call me?
你要干什么?
The fuck are you doing?
你知道我是谁?
Do you know who I am?
你以为你能逃得了 你会......
If you think you'll get away with this, you got...
见鬼!
Goddamn it!
别这样!
Stop!
你要什么我给什么 只是求你别杀我
I'll give you anything you want. Just, please, don't kill me.
你好 鲍勃
Hello, buddy-boy.
迪克·琼斯在此恭候
Dick Jones here.
我想你现在
I guess you're on your knees about now...
一定在跪地求饶吧
...begging for your life.
真可怜
Pathetic.
你不再心高气傲了吗?
You don't feel so cocky now, do you?
他给你多少 我给你双倍
Whatever he's paying you, I'll double it right now.
你知道最可悲的是什么?
You know what the tragedy is here?
我们是可以做朋友的
We could have been friends.
但你违反常规
But you wouldn't go through proper channels.
越级报告
You went over my head.
那侮辱了我
That hurt.
生活还要继续 这是个老故事 为了爱和名誉而奋斗
But life goes on. It's an old story, the fight for love and glory.
如果你认为这是个游戏 会对你有帮助的
It helps if you think of it as a game.
每一个游戏都有胜利者
Every game has a winner...
和失败者
...and a loser.
你出局了 鲍勃
I'm cashing you out, Bob.
我可不想出这么多钱 萨尔
I don't think I want to pay that, Sal.
我不能再让了 价格不能再低了
I don't give a shit what you want. I set the prices here.
听着萨尔 或许你不知道 我是底特律的老大
Listen, Sal, maybe you haven't heard. I'm the guy who owns Detroit.
你想从这捞一笔
You want space in my marketplace...
就得先给我一些
...you'll have to give me a volume discount.
我不会减价的
Not into discounts.
约翰逊 给他看看我们带来的圣诞礼物
Joe, show the man what we brought him for Christmas.
考虑一下 兄弟 好生意是不会送上门的
Think about it, chum. Good business is where you find it.
好的 让我来挑明
Okay, let me try to put this in perspective.
你杀了许多警察
You've killed a bunch of cops.
谣传你们在警方有后台
Word around is that you've got a lot of heavy connections downtown.
你让我的许多朋友不安
You make a lot of my friends nervous.
许多人
A lot of people...
希望看到我
...want to see a guy like me...
把你杀了
...put a guy like you out of business.
我不知道
I don't know.
或许我也没说清
Maybe I'm just not making myself clear.
我不想和你纠缠 萨尔
I don't want to fuck with you, Sal.
但是我在警方有后台
But I got the connections.
我有销售网络
I got the sales organization.
我有能力
I got the muscle to shove enough of this factory...
让你这蠢货
...so far up your stupid wop ass...
吃不了兜着走
...that you'll shit snow for a year.
弗兰克 杀了他
Frankie, blow this cocksucker's head off.
你想动枪!
Guns, guns, guns!
来啊 萨尔!
Come on, Sal!
老虎队今晚有场比赛
The Tigers are playing tonight.
我从不错过比赛
I never miss a game.
开个玩笑
Just kidding.
快走!
Go!
定位
慢慢下来 不然会有麻烦的
Come quietly, or there will be trouble.
他妈的!
Fuck you!
哦 见鬼!
Oh, shit!
克拉伦斯·伯蒂迪克
Clarence Boddicker...
你被捕了
...you are under arrest.
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
去你的!
Fuck you!
嗨 等一下 等一下!
Hey, wait a minute. Wait a minute!
我有权利的 我是受保护的!
I'm protected, man. I've got protection!
-你有权找律师辩护 -你在干什么?
- You have the right to an attorney. - What is this shit?!
该死
Goddamn it.
该死!听我说!听我说!
Goddamn it! Listen to me! Listen to me, you fuck!
主谋是另一个人!他是OCP的 他是高级主管
It's another guy! He's OCP. He's the senior president.
你所说的话将成为呈堂证供
Anything you say may be used against you.
是迪克·琼斯!
It's Dick Jones!
你不明白吗 呆子?
Don't you care, you cocksucker?
我为迪克·琼斯卖命!
I work for Dick Jones!
迪克·琼斯!
Dick Jones !
他是OCP的二把手!警察归OCP管!
He's the number two guy at OCP! OCP runs the cops!
你是警察!
You're a cop!
警察
Cop...
准则3:维护法律
是的 我是警察
Yes, I am a cop.
拘捕模式
我也不想那样 但听我说!
I don't like it either, but listen!
听我说 笨蛋!
You listen to me, asshole!
你现在在说的是解散整个城市的警察
You're talking about shutting down a major metropolitan police force!
没有警察 这里会变得一团糟!
Without cops, this city would tear itself apart!
工会昨天投票通过罢工的提议
The union voted for a strike last night!
我们每周要死五个人!
We lost five guys last week!
我们忍受不了了
We're getting creamed out there.
把他归案
Book him.
什么罪名?
What's the charge?
杀害警察
He's a cop killer.
去你的!
Shit!
把电话给我
Just give me my fucking phone call.
我知道 律师会在二十四小时内把你保出来
I understand. The lawyers will have you out in 24 hours.
你只要保持沉默
Just don't say anything else.
我的天 你惹大麻烦了
Jesus, you really screwed up.
回放
回放 克拉伦斯·伯蒂迪克 资料编码F59085202492
你不明白吗?
Don't you care?
我为迪克·琼斯卖命!迪克·琼斯!
I work for Dick Jones! Dick Jones!
我为迪克·琼斯卖命!
I work for Dick Jones!
他控制OCP!警察归OCP管!
He runs OCP! OCP runs the cops!
过来 警员
Come in, officer.
没有预约 我是不见人的
I don't usually see anyone without an appointment...
但你是个例外
...but in your case, I'll make an exception.
你被捕了
You are under arrest.
拘捕模式
以什么罪名?
On what charge?
协助及教唆他人犯罪
Aiding and abetting a known felon.
违反刑法第六款一百四十八条
看来我遇到大麻烦了
Sounds like I'm in a lot of trouble.
把我带走吧
Better take me in.
我会的
I will.
产品违例
准则4
Directive 4.
怎么了 警员?
What's the matter, officer?
我来告诉你是怎么回事
I'll tell you what's the matter.
一个小小的保险规则"准则4 "
It's a little insurance policy called "Directive 4."
是我对你心理的小小改动
My little contribution to your psychological profile.
试图逮捕OCP高层官员将导致机器失灵
Any attempt to arrest a senior officer of OCP results in shutdown.
准则4
Directive 4.
你认为怎么样?
What did you think?
以为和以前一样是个普通的警员?
That you were an ordinary police officer?
你是我们的产品
You're our product...
我们不会让我们的产品同我们作对
...and we can't have our products turning against us.
准则4
Directive 4
你还在负隅顽抗
Still a little fight left in you.
准则4
Directive 4
或许你想见我的一位朋友
Maybe you'd like to meet a friend of mine.
我杀鲍勃·莫顿是因为他犯了个错误
I had to kill Bob Morton because he made a mistake.
现在要清除这个错误
Now it's time to erase that mistake.
找赫吉科克来!大楼有麻烦了!
Get me Hedgecock! There's trouble in the tower!
准备开火
Prepare to fire.
-等一下! -我的天 他是个警察!
- Wait a second! - He's a cop, for God's sake!
-你不能那么做! -我们奉命摧毁他!
- You can't do that! - We have orders to destroy it!
-哦 老天! -你疯了!
- Oh, shit! - You're maniacs!
自由射击!
Fire at will!
推进!
Move in!
墨菲 是我
Murphy, it's me.
露易丝
Lewis.
三楼!他在三楼!
Level three! He's on level three!
在这 在这!
Over here, over here!
开火!
Open fire!
在后面
It's back.
大的在后面 因为越大越好
Big is back. Because bigger is better.
6000 SUX 品质一贯优良 美国制造
6000 SUX, an American tradition.
晚上好 现在由杰斯帕金斯和凯西王为您报道
Good evening. I'm Jess Perkins with Casey Wong.
首先是巴西圣芭芭拉的报道
Top story: Santa Barbara.
一万英亩的树林和房子
Ten thousand acres of wooded residential land...
毁于一旦
...were scorched in an instant when a laser canon...
这是由于战略防御平台的激光炮
...aboard the Strategic Defense Peace Platform...
在今天的日常测试中误射
...misfired today during routine tests.
到目前为止
It was a day of mourning for the families...
已知一百一十三人丧生
...of 113 people known dead at this hour.
其中有两名前美国总统
Among them, two former U.S. presidents...
他们是在圣芭芭拉安度晚年的
...who had retired in the Santa Barbara area.
今天全国哀悼一天
A day of mourning for a country.
今天 警察工会与OCP继续谈判
Police union representatives and OCP continued negotiations today...
希望能阻止计划于明天午夜开始的
...in hopes of averting a citywide strike by police...
全市性警察罢工
...scheduled to begin tomorrow at midnight.
下面由贾斯廷巴拉德-沃特金斯报道
Justin Ballard-Watkins has more.
今天他们仍在执勤 但是明天呢?
They're still on duty. But what about tomorrow?
这是放在被犯罪困扰的 莱克星顿区居民前的问题
That's the question we put to people in the crime-plagued Lexington area.
他们是公仆 他们工作稳定
They're public servants. They got job security.
他们不应该罢工
They're not supposed to strike.
这是个自由社会
It's a free society.
但毫无自由可言 因为生命都没有保障
Except there ain't nothing free, because there's no guarantees.
只能靠你自己 这就是弱肉强食
You're on your own. That's the law of the jungle.
-小心点 -请让一下
- Be very careful. - Excuse me, please.
他们在重新装修
Remodeling.
你好 芭芭拉
Hi, Barbara.
听着 我要见迪克·琼斯
Listen, I'm here to see Dick Jones.
办完事后 我还有时间
But when I'm done, I've got some free time.
或许你可以陪陪我
Maybe you could fit me in.
他在等你 伯蒂迪克先生
He's expecting you, Mr. Boddicker.
口香糖给你
You can keep the gum.
你好 迪克 成功了吗?
Hey, Dickie-boy. How's tricks?
那东西还活着
That thing is still alive.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
那个要拘捕你的 让你胆战心惊的警察
The police officer who arrested you, the one you spilled your guts to.
看看我的脸 迪克 他要杀了我
Take a look at my face, Dick. He was trying to kill me.
他是机器人 傻瓜!
He's a cyborg, you idiot!
他录下了你所说的每一句话
He recorded every word you said.
他的记忆可以作为证据!
His memory's admissible as evidence!
你把我拖下水了!
You involved me!
你要杀了他
You'll have to kill it.
听着
Well, listen, chief.
是你们公司造出来那鬼东西
Your company built the fucking thing.
现在要我来解决他?
Now I gotta deal with it?
我没时间去对付他!
I don't have time for this bullshit!
随你的便 但是三角城两个月后开始建造
Suit yourself. But Delta City begins construction in two months.
两百万工人住在拖车上
That's 2 million workers living in trailers.
那意味着毒品、赌博和卖淫......
That means drugs, gambling, prostitution.
是个大展宏图的机会
Virgin territory for the man who knows how to open up new markets.
一个人可以主宰一切
One man could control it all...
克拉伦斯
...Clarence.
毕竟我们是朋友
Well, I guess we're gonna be friends after all.
理查德
Richard.
毁了他
Destroy it.
我要一些重型武器
Gonna need some major firepower.
能弄到军用装备吗?
You got access to military weaponry?
我们就是军队
We practically are the military.
你把枪带来了吗?
Did you bring the gun?
到处看不到警察 今天有一半人没上岗
The precinct was deserted. Half the force didn't show up for work today.
每个人都在午夜离开了 我想这是在罢工
Everyone else walks out at midnight. I guess we're on strike.
我不知道你想要什么
I wasn't sure what you needed.
我随便拿了一些
I sort of grabbed things.
你的枪
Your gun.
这是你要的吗?
You asked for this?
我给你带了些吃的
I brought you some food.
不 谢谢
No, thank you.
我不饿
I'm not hungry.
你可能不想看到
You may not like what you're going to see.
很高兴再见到你 墨菲
It's really good to see you again, Murphy.
墨菲有一个老婆和一个孩子 他们在哪?
Murphy had a wife and son. Where are they?
在葬礼之后
Well, after the funeral...
-她离开了 -他们去哪了?
...she moved away. - Where did they go?
她认为你死了
She thought you were dead.
她重新开始了
She started over again.
我感觉得到他们
I can feel them.
但我记不清他们了
But I can't remember them.
让我一个人待一会
Leave me alone.
生日快乐 大卫 我把她送给你
Happy birthday, Dave. She's from me.
嗨 我同时能拥有你们两个吗?
Well, hey, can I have you both?
当然!
Sure!
我们已经注射过免疫了
We've had our shots.
我要用一元买美女
I'd buy that for a dollar.
嗨 埃米尔 监狱怎么样?
Hey, Emil. How's the Gray Bar Hotel?
还好 他们把体恤还给我了 也没人为难我
Not bad. They let me keep the shirt. And nobody popped my cherry.
埃米尔 怎么样?很高兴见到你
Emil, how you doing, man? Good to see you.
他们把我放了出来
I get out of jail for free,
然后我在监狱停车场找到了这个......
then I find this in the prison parking lot.
刚刚出场的全新6000 SUX!
A brand-new 6000 SUX. Still got the factory sticker on it!
嗨 克拉伦斯!
Hey, Clarence!
乔伊的车和你一样!
Joey's got a car just like yours, man!
克拉伦斯 你认为怎么样?
Clarence, what do you think, buddy?
你拿的是什么 克拉伦斯?
What do you got there, Clarence, huh?
哦 新玩具 我能玩玩吗?
Whoa, a new toy. Can I play?
看着吧
Watch this.
等一下 等一下!
Wait a minute. Wait a minute!
啊 妈的!
Aw, shit!
-去你的! -好车子 乔伊
- Fuck! - Nice car, Joe.
-他妈的 克拉伦斯 -给我试试
- Fuck you, Clarence. - Let me try that.
眼镜蛇炮 最新科技成果 乓 乓
Cobra assault canon. State-of-the-art. Bang, bang.
我喜欢它!
I like it!
-给我试试 小个子 -拿你自己的!
- Give it up, faggot little man. - Get your own!
给他吧!
Come on!
再来一个 埃米尔!
Do it, Emil!
看看这个!你们抱头鼠窜吧!
Check this out! Heads up, you guys!
他在钢厂 我们走
He's in the steel mill. Let's go.
好的 让他粉身碎骨!我们出发
All right, cut the horseshit! We're moving out.
快点 埃米尔!你开货车
Come on, Emil! Get your ass in the van.
大家伙 快点!我们走!
Come on, lard-ass! Let's move it!
别吵我 小个子!
Forget you, faggot!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我的瞄准系统有一些误差
My targeting system is a little messed up.
我能帮你吗?
Can I help you?
帮我瞄准
Aim for me.
-锁定了吗? -好了
- Are you locked in now? - Yes.
向左偏一些
A little more to the left.
这儿
Here.
-我想你已经恢复了 -谢谢
- I figure that's dead-on. - Thank you.
快点 我们要干掉他!
Come on, man, let's smoke him!
毁灭小组在此!那个机器人呢?
The wrecking crew is here! Where is that mother...?
不在那儿!
Give that up, man!
别玩花的 杀了他们 埃米尔!
Nothing fancy. Just kill him. Emil!
-什么? -上车
- What? - In the van.
-你应该离开这儿 -嗨 我们是搭档
- You should get out of here now. - Hey, we're partners.
把车开来
Get the car.
该死 妈的!
Damn it. Shit!
找我吗?
Looking for me?
杀了他!
Cut him off!
快点!快!别让他跑了!去吧!
Come on! Go on! Cut him off! Go, go!
好的!我抓住你了!
Okay! Now I got you!
"危险 有毒废料"
救救我
Help me.
别碰我!
Don't touch me, man!
救救我
Help me.
见鬼!
Shit!
-再见 宝贝儿 -克拉伦斯!
- Bye-bye, baby. - Clarence!
好的
Okay.
我投降
I give up.
我要杀了你
I'm not arresting you anymore.
嗨 先等一下
Hey. Now, wait a second.
等一下 你太感情用事
Wait a minute. You're taking this kind of personal.
来呀
Come on, man.
你让我紧张 来呀 你不会杀我的
You're making me nervous. Come on, you can't do this.
来呀!别胡来!嗨 嗨!
Come on now! Don't mess around! Hey. Hey!
现在别假慈悲了!
Now, don't get cute!
死吧 怪物!
Die, you bastard!
耶!耶!
Yeah! Yeah!
好的!好的!
All right! All right!
我搞定他了 克拉伦斯!我搞定他了!
I got him, Clarence! I got him!
永别了 机械战警!
Sayonara, Robocop!
露易丝!
Lewis !
墨菲 我快不行了
Murphy, I'm a mess.
他们会治好你的
They'll fix you.
他们什么都能治
They fix everything.
警察罢工对我们很有利
The police strike could work for us.
我们的ED 209型将取代警察
We can have ED 209s in place all over the city...
希望得到大众的支持
...and expect immediate public support.
现在已有一个在楼下守卫
I've got one downstairs guarding the building now.
你在私人领地非法停车
You're illegally parked on private property.
限你在二十秒内把车开走
You have 20 seconds to move your vehicle.
不论发生什么
Whatever happens...
公司都会继承创始人的理念......
...this corporation will live up to its guiding principles:
勇气、强壮、信念
Courage, strength, conviction.
勇往直前地去迎接每一个挑战
We will meet each new challenge with the same aggressive attitude.
警员 你有什么事吗?
How can we help you, officer?
我要以谋杀罪逮捕迪克·琼斯
Dick Jones is wanted for murder.
真可笑!这东西出毛病了!
This is absurd! That thing is a violent mechanical psychopath!
我的程序不允许我拘捕公司的雇员
My program will not allow me to act against an officer of this company.
这个指控可不是儿戏 你的证据呢?
These are serious charges. What is your evidence?
我杀鲍勃·莫顿是因为他犯了个错误
I had to kill Bob Morton because he made a mistake.
现在要清除这个错误
Now it's time to erase that mistake.
我杀鲍勃·莫顿是因为他犯了个错误
I had to kill Bob Morton because he made a mistake.
现在要清除这个错误
Now it's time to erase that mistake.
我现在就要架直升机!
I want a chopper! Now!
准则4
Directive 4
慢慢走到天台上去
We will walk to the roof very calmly.
我会带人质上直升机
I will board the chopper with my hostage.
如果有人阻止我
Anybody tries to stop me...
我就杀了这老家伙
...the old geezer gets it.
准则4
Directive 4
迪克 你被解雇了!
Dick, you're fired!
谢谢你
Thank you.
好枪法 你叫什么名字?
Nice shooting, son. What's your name?
墨菲
Murphy.